collegeinfousa.com 2009-04-13

# CollegeInfoUSA.com - Privacy Policy

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**  
This privacy policy covers how College Info USA, Inc. treats personal information that College Info USA, Inc. collects and receives. Personal information is information you provide about yourself that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, email address, or phone number and that is not otherwise publicly available. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices or the content of websites of companies that College Info USA, Inc. links to, does not own or control, or to people that College Info USA, Inc. does not employ or manage.

**Information We Collect**  
In order to ensure that consumers get the very best service, College Info USA, Inc. collects demographic information, web pages visited and other consumer-volunteered information from sources such as forms, and/or site registrations. College Info USA, Inc.' s request forms may require users to give us information such as your name, address, phone number, social security number, e-mail address and certain financial and credit-related information. This information gathering procedure allows College Info USA, Inc. to match you with a dealer or partner that we feel is best able to fulfill your request. This information also helps College Info USA, Inc. in the development or referral of products and services that we believe will meet the continuing needs of our customers. Collected information is used to improve the content of our website, customize the content and/or layout of our website for individual users, and to contact users for marketing purposes as well as route requests to our auto dealer network, fulfillment and marketing partners. . Should you request an auto loan quote such information will be distributed to our partners for credit checks and loan approval.

**Children's Guidelines**  
Although this site is intended for the use of adults, and is not of likely interest to children, the forms on this site are capable of collecting online contact information from children who furnish it without prior parental consent or parental notification. Upon discovery that any such information may be supplied by children, such information shall be disregarded and deleted.

**Personalization**  
College Info USA, Inc. offers its users the advantage of personalization on our Web site by using cookies. Web site personalization provides our customers with a more convenient online experience and is at no given time used to track information or retrieve data from your hard drive.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web server may transfer to your computer through your web browser. When this information is stored on your computer, our system is able to recognize your browser and in turn customize web page content for you. We will not use any cookies to retrieve data from your hard drive or obtain sensitive information about you. When a cookie is set, your browser will check it for length, an expiration date, and where it originated. Only unitedautofinance.com can access the cookies that we set. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain online services or website features on unitedautofinance.com.

**Security**  
College Info USA, Inc. understands the importance of security for our consumers. When applicable, we use the latest SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology to protect sensitive personal or financial information during transmission. This allows your personal information to be submitted in a secure environment while reaching the intended parties. An SSL-capable web browser is needed to support this encryption technology. Netscape Navigator 4.6 or higher or Microsoft's Internet Explorer 4.01 or higher will support SSL technology. To verify that you are on a secure web page in Netscape Navigator, right-click while your cursor is on the form (not the border) and select "view Frame information" in Netscape Navigator. To view security certificates in Internet Explorer, click Internet Options on the View menu in the browser and then the Content tab. In the Certificates area, click the Personal, Sites, and Publishers buttons to view the current certificates.

**Information We Share With Others**  
College Info USA, Inc. may decide to share your personal information with trusted marketing partners who work on behalf of or with College Info USA, Inc. under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help College Info USA, Inc. communicate with you about offers from College Info USA, Inc. or to inform you about their products and services. (See below if you prefer that we not share this information). Occasionally, when College Info USA, Inc. is not able to directly fulfill your request, we may forward your request for information to another reputable partner or auto dealer. In such a case, you will become subject to the security and privacy policies that are posted on the associated website and if you wish to do so, you will have to opt out of disclosure through the associated website. In those cases where College Info USA, Inc. decides to share your information with marketing partners, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. College Info USA, Inc. also responds to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, violations of College Info USA, Inc. terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Ownership of the Information**  
Once it is received in the College Info USA, Inc. database, all request form information, including your name, e-mail address, home address, financial and credit information becomes the property of College Info USA, Inc.. This information is passed on to our banking, dealer and fulfillment partners and affiliates for the execution of the order, service or request. Once one of these entities receives this information, it becomes subject to their respective privacy policy, in addition to College Info USA, Inc.'s privacy policy. Our partners use this information to process your order, to approve your credit and to provide valuable services. If you opt out on our website we will not provide your information to partners. If you do not opt out on our website, any requests to opt out of future partner communications must be made directly to the Partner.

**Third Party Partner Privacy Policies**  
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to dealers or other parties that you are placed in contact with through our site or other sites throughout the Internet, different privacy policies may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since College Info USA, Inc. does not control the privacy policies of third parties or partners, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party or partner and we encourage you to read their privacy policies or ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using this site and providing us with your information, you agree to the College Info USA, Inc. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page frequently for changes. Your continued use of the College Info USA, Inc. site means you accept those changes. You can e-mail us with any further questions you may have.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page frequently for changes. Your continued use of the College Info USA, Inc. site means you accept those changes. You can e-mail us with any further questions you may have.

**How to Request Opt Out**  
Many customers appreciate receiving information and offers about products and services that may be of interest and value to them. However, at College Info USA, Inc., we recognize that it's your choice. If you prefer that we not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to any nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures, that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law). If you do not want us to share any information that you have provided to us or that we have gathered, please let us know by e-mailing us. Please include your name, address, and other identification information and any other applicable information. Your request will apply to any of the information we have obtained in any transaction, such as your request forms. If you have any other questions or concerns regarding your privacy at College Info USA, Inc. or wish to opt out of disclosure of your information, you may email our customer service department at privacy@UnitedAutoFinance.com. It may take 10 days from the time we receive your request to opt out to remove you from our database. Please be aware that you may still receive offers during while your request is being processed.
